{"results":

[{"question":"How many sides -not counting the bottom- does the great pyramid of Egypt have?",	 
"correct_answer":"8","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What year did Marty and Doc travel to in Back to the Future part two?",
"correct_answer":"2015","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"How many dots are there on two dice?",
"correct_answer":"42","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"How many squares are there on a chess board?",
"correct_answer":"64", "incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What year did Elvis Presley die?",	 
"correct_answer":"1977","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"How many bones are in the human body?",
"correct_answer":"206","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What number US President was Barack Obama?",
"correct_answer":"44","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"True or false - Australia is the world's largest island?",
"correct_answer":"true","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What year did Melbourne host the Olympic games?",
"correct_answer":"1956","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"True or false - green is a primary colour",
"correct_answer":"false","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"At what age is a wizard admitted to Hogwarts?",	 
"correct_answer":"11","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"How many valves does a trumpet have?",
"correct_answer":"3","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What number planet is Uranus from the sun?",
"correct_answer":"7","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"In miles - what is the diameter of planet earth?",	 
"correct_answer":"8000","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"How many Lord of the Rings movies did Peter Jackson direct?",	 
"correct_answer":"3","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"A male kangaroo is called a boomer, and a female is called a what?", 
"correct_answer":"flyer","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"By what name is the bird 'Pica Pica' better known?", 
"correct_answer":"magpie","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"In what kind of tree would one find a Kookaburra sitting in?", 
"correct_answer":"Gum","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What is Michael Jackson's middle name?", 
"correct_answer":"Joseph","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What is another name for tetanus?", 
"correct_answer":"lockjaw","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What is Australia's longest river?", 
"correct_answer":"Murray","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What is the gift given at a 40th wedding?",
"correct_answer":"ruby","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What is the only flexible murder weapon in the game 'Cluedo'?", 
"correct_answer":"rope","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What is the world's largest rodent?", 
"correct_answer":"capybara","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What is the world's most popular spice?", 
"correct_answer":"pepper","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What kind of bird is a macaw?",
"correct_answer":"parrot","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"How many degrees can the great horned owl turn its head?", 
"correct_answer":"270","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What kind of biscuits were named after Australian & New Zealand soldiers?", 
"correct_answer":"ANZAC","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What part of New York City was called 'broken land' by the Dutch?", 
"correct_answer":"Brooklyn","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What planet has a pink sky?", 
"correct_answer":"Mars","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"Which computer manufacturer in 1984 advertised their new computer during the Superbowl?", 
"correct_answer":"Apple","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"Which invention did Mark Twain become the first famous author to use?", 
"correct_answer":"typewriter","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"Which is the only Australian state capital that is not named after a person?", 
"correct_answer":"Perth","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What is the offspring of a female horse and a male donkey?", 
"correct_answer":"Mule","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What Viking god is Thursday named after?", 
"correct_answer":"Thor","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},

{"question":"What name is given to a boxer who leads with his right hand?", 
"correct_answer":"Southpaw","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]}]}